let savollar21 = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "to appear",
        answer: "A. ko'rinmoq",
        options: [
            "A. ko'rinmoq",
            "B. g'oyib bo'lmoq",
            "C. yashirinmoq",
            "D. e'tiborsiz qoldirmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "base",
        answer: "B. asos",
        options: [
            "A. cho'qqi",
            "B. asos",
            "C. o'rtasi",
            "D. chekka"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "brain",
        answer: "C. miya",
        options: [
            "A. yurak",
            "B. o'pka",
            "C. miya",
            "D. oshqozon"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "career",
        answer: "D. faoliyat",
        options: [
            "A. hobi",
            "B. vazifa",
            "C. ish kuni",
            "D. faoliyat"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "clerk",
        answer: "A. do'kon xodimi",
        options: [
            "A. do'kon xodimi",
            "B. mijoz",
            "C. menejer",
            "D. egasi"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "effort",
        answer: "B. harakat",
        options: [
            "A. osonlik",
            "B. harakat",
            "C. bekorchilik",
            "D. dangasalik"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "to enter",
        answer: "C. kirmoq",
        options: [
            "A. chiqish",
            "B. chetlashmoq",
            "C. kirmoq",
            "D. chiqib ketmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "excellent",
        answer: "A. a'lo",
        options: [
            "A. a'lo",
            "B. yomon",
            "C. o'rtacha",
            "D. yetarli emas"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "hero",
        answer: "D. qahramon",
        options: [
            "A. qo'rqoq",
            "B. tomoshabin",
            "C. yovuz odam",
            "D. qahramon"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "to hurry",
        answer: "B. shoshilmoq",
        options: [
            "A. sekin yurmoq",
            "B. shoshilmoq",
            "C. turgan joyida qolmoq",
            "D. sayr qilmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "to inform",
        answer: "A. xabar bermoq",
        options: [
            "A. xabar bermoq",
            "B. e'tiborsiz qoldirmoq",
            "C. yolg'on gapirmoq",
            "D. jim bo'lmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "later",
        answer: "B. keyinroq",
        options: [
            "A. oldinroq",
            "B. keyinroq",
            "C. darhol",
            "D. hech qachon"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "to leave",
        answer: "A. tark etmoq",
        options: [
            "A. tark etmoq",
            "B. qolmoq",
            "C. kelmoq",
            "D. kirish"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "to locate",
        answer: "D. topmoq",
        options: [
            "A. yo'qotmoq",
            "B. yashirmoq",
            "C. unutmoq",
            "D. topmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "nurse",
        answer: "A. hamshira",
        options: [
            "A. hamshira",
            "B. shifokor",
            "C. bemor",
            "D. tashrif buyuruvchi"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "operation",
        answer: "C. operatsiya",
        options: [
            "A. tekshiruv",
            "B. maslahat",
            "C. operatsiya",
            "D. davolash"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "pain",
        answer: "B. og'riq",
        options: [
            "A. xursandchilik",
            "B. og'riq",
            "C. lazzat",
            "D. baxt"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "to refuse",
        answer: "A. rad etmoq",
        options: [
            "A. rad etmoq",
            "B. qabul qilmoq",
            "C. so'ramoq",
            "D. tasdiqlamoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "though",
        answer: "B. ga qaramasdan",
        options: [
            "A. chunki",
            "B. ga qaramasdan",
            "C. agar",
            "D. uchun"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: "various",
        answer: "D. turli xil",
        options: [
            "A. bir xil",
            "B. o'xshash",
            "C. yagona",
            "D. turli xil"
        ]
    }
];
